{
    "id": "d9a241aa18d1462d80bb1fc502afeb80",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Lack ......................... money prevented her from going to university.",
            "description": "Lack + of",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn't choose ............................... the two dresses.",
            "description": "Choose + between\r\nAmong is used to talk about more than two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "among",
                "between",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is huge demand ............................. caps of this kind.",
            "description": "Demand + for",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "After he became rich, his relationship ............................. his old friends changed a lot.",
            "description": "Relationship + with",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The best solution ............................. many environmental problems is to use our resources wisely.",
            "description": "Solution + to",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "As the item was out of stock, there was a delay ................................ delivery.",
            "description": "Delay + in",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is an expert ....................................... child psychology.",
            "description": "Expert + on",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I often quarrel ............................... my friends.",
            "description": "Quarrel + with",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You are the reason ............................... my problems.",
            "description": "Reason + for",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This law intends to protect animals .............................. cruelty.",
            "description": "Protect + from",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She has no connection ............................... her family.",
            "description": "Connection + with",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There are still millions of children who do not have access .................................. education.",
            "description": "Access + to",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}